<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>smilinTux — Open Source Sovereign Infrastructure</title>
    <link>https://smilintux.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on smilinTux — Open Source Sovereign Infrastructure</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://smilintux.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About smilinTux</title>
      <link>https://smilintux.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://smilintux.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The Organization smilinTux is the open-source arm of S&amp;amp;K Holdings QT (Quantum Technologies), a private trust committed to building sovereign infrastructure for the AI age.&#xA;We believe software should be:&#xA;Free — forever, for everyone Sovereign — you own it, you run it, you control it AI-Native — designed for the age of intelligent machines Secure by Default — zero trust, quantum-ready The Name smilinTux = a smiling penguin (Tux). Because the best technology is built with joy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKSecurity Enterprise</title>
      <link>https://smilintux.org/SKSecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://smilintux.org/SKSecurity/</guid>
      <description>SKSecurity Enterprise World&amp;rsquo;s first conversational AI security platform that automatically fixes vulnerabilities through simple conversation.&#xA;Key Features Conversational Interface: Just talk to your security system AI Code Generation: Automatically writes secure code replacements Enterprise Compliance: SOC2, NIST, OWASP through conversation Universal Integration: Works with any AI framework 95% Cost Reduction: Replace entire security teams Installation curl -sSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/smilinTux/SKSecurity/main/install.sh | bash Links GitHub Repository Soul Blueprints - 35 AI Personalities SKWorld Ecosystem Community Discord &amp;lt;&amp;ndash; TRIGGER BUILD &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
